[{"answer": "Thanks.", "docId": "120907pmt", "aSentId": 23, "question": "You're quite fascinating, aren't you?", "qSentId": 22}, {"answer": "Well, it means that there's this -- as Joaquin has said many times.", "docId": "120907pmt", "aSentId": 110, "question": "How do you reinforce the kind of story that you guys can tell America?", "qSentId": 109}, {"answer": "Well, what I think is that when folks compare where the nation was when President Obama took office and you heard several speakers say that, losing 750,000 to 800,000 jobs a month and then you compare where we are now, 29 straight months of private sector job growth, 4.5 million new jobs, that I'm confident he's going to lay out the case very convincingly for why even though we haven't made the -- we're not where we want to be, we have made significant progress.", "docId": "120907pmt", "aSentId": 130, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 129}, {"answer": "I am incensed --", "docId": "120907pmt", "aSentId": 166, "question": "How fired up are you about this election?", "qSentId": 165}, {"answer": "I think the most exciting -- may be exciting for me because I'm over here on the left.", "docId": "120907pmt", "aSentId": 173, "question": "What do you think of the way they've been going at each other and the issues that are likely to be the determining issues?", "qSentId": 172}, {"answer": "I don't think as a party they have a clear directive anymore.", "docId": "120907pmt", "aSentId": 184, "question": "Are you voting for the party?", "qSentId": 183}, {"answer": "Well, yes, probably.", "docId": "120907pmt", "aSentId": 220, "question": "Do you think that the dream that you grew up with has changed?", "qSentId": 219}, {"answer": "Of course it is.", "docId": "120907pmt", "aSentId": 229, "question": "The whole thing about Pussy Riots in Russia was ridiculous, wasn't it?", "qSentId": 228}, {"answer": "Yes, I had to find a vehicle big enough for my ego.", "docId": "120907pmt", "aSentId": 282, "question": "Then the traditional singer goes off and, you know, wants to be the new Michael Jackson, right?", "qSentId": 281}, {"answer": "Well, you know, we were because I think in the middle of the solo records we did the greatest hits.", "docId": "120907pmt", "aSentId": 287, "question": "What was it like the second time around to get back with the group and do your thing again?", "qSentId": 286}, {"answer": "ORGAN: Yes.", "docId": "120907pmt", "aSentId": 314, "question": "He wears those -- like all he wears is like the jogging suits, right?", "qSentId": 313}, {"answer": "Well, I have a guitar here for you to take a look at.", "docId": "120907pmt", "aSentId": 329, "question": "Hey, how can I help you?", "qSentId": 328}, {"answer": "I got this from my father.", "docId": "120907pmt", "aSentId": 332, "question": "Where in the world did you get this?", "qSentId": 331}, {"answer": "That's sort of a misnomer.", "docId": "120907pmt", "aSentId": 343, "question": "Is it because, in fact, ironically, America is suffering economically and when that happens, a business like yours tends to do well?", "qSentId": 342}, {"answer": "It's everybody, especially our store.", "docId": "120907pmt", "aSentId": 358, "question": "I mean who comes in your store?", "qSentId": 357}, {"answer": "That happens actually a lot.", "docId": "120907pmt", "aSentId": 367, "question": "I know there must be a lot of surprises, but when you look back, what have been the moments you go, wow, when somebody's brought something in that's really knocked your socks off?", "qSentId": 366}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120907pmt", "aSentId": 371, "question": "This is actually the battle plan for Iwo Jima, is that right?", "qSentId": 370}, {"answer": "It was a person, his father had been on Iwo Jima.", "docId": "120907pmt", "aSentId": 375, "question": "Who brought this in?", "qSentId": 374}, {"answer": ".", "docId": "120907pmt", "aSentId": 380, "question": "How do you assess a value?", "qSentId": 379}, {"answer": "I think is it was right around $3,500, something like that.", "docId": "120907pmt", "aSentId": 387, "question": "Would you remember even the ballpark?", "qSentId": 386}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120907pmt", "aSentId": 398, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 397}, {"answer": "Eight thousand dollars or an Iwo Jima plan, I'll take the 8 grand.", "docId": "120907pmt", "aSentId": 403, "question": "So 8 grand, it's coming off the wall right?", "qSentId": 402}, {"answer": "Yes, I -- I think his story was basically that he, you know, he got injured, wasn't able to compete in 2000 and was doing some other things.", "docId": "120907pmt", "aSentId": 416, "question": "So, do you remember his story?", "qSentId": 415}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "120907pmt", "aSentId": 419, "question": "ORGAN: So do you remember his story?", "qSentId": 418}, {"answer": "That's a very difficult thing, because they rarely if ever get on the market.", "docId": "120907pmt", "aSentId": 425, "question": "What were they -- how do you quantify an Olympic medal?", "qSentId": 424}, {"answer": "Actually, I gave him a loan on them.", "docId": "120907pmt", "aSentId": 431, "question": "Do you remember what you paid him for it?", "qSentId": 430}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120907pmt", "aSentId": 437, "question": "So he'll never get them back?", "qSentId": 436}, {"answer": "It's sad but --", "docId": "120907pmt", "aSentId": 439, "question": "Sad, isn't it?", "qSentId": 438}, {"answer": "One of the things is a pawn broker with a heart is usually a pawn broker out of business.", "docId": "120907pmt", "aSentId": 441, "question": "Do you ever feel sad, or is the lesson you hand down to your son, you can't afford to get emotionally involved?", "qSentId": 440}, {"answer": "Yeah --", "docId": "120907pmt", "aSentId": 448, "question": "Is there anything you would turn down?", "qSentId": 447}, {"answer": "We won't take any German World War II items.", "docId": "120907pmt", "aSentId": 450, "question": "ORGAN: Have you ever turned anything down?", "qSentId": 449}, {"answer": "I won't do it.", "docId": "120907pmt", "aSentId": 452, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 451}, {"answer": "I mean, just anything in that area.", "docId": "120907pmt", "aSentId": 464, "question": "Is there any other sort of thing you feel strongly you wouldn't want to be party to?", "qSentId": 463}, {"answer": "It's a real easy one.", "docId": "120907pmt", "aSentId": 473, "question": "And I suppose the obvious question is what is the most expensive thing that you've ever bought?", "qSentId": 472}, {"answer": "Oh, yeah, every day.", "docId": "120907pmt", "aSentId": 477, "question": "Do people actually walk in with gold bars?", "qSentId": 476}, {"answer": "I can't remember what it was.", "docId": "120907pmt", "aSentId": 479, "question": "Tell us the biggest -- what's the biggest chunk of gold you've ever had to deal with?", "qSentId": 478}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120907pmt", "aSentId": 482, "question": "Five hundred thousand dollars, really?", "qSentId": 481}, {"answer": "In our shop, it's weird.", "docId": "120907pmt", "aSentId": 486, "question": "What is the -- if you're smart, what is the markup if you move quickly on something like that?", "qSentId": 485}, {"answer": "One percent I'm happy with.", "docId": "120907pmt", "aSentId": 490, "question": "So on that kind of thing, that huge amount of gold?", "qSentId": 489}, {"answer": "I mean, it's a lot of people don't understand we're in business, would say, I would never do that for one percent.", "docId": "120907pmt", "aSentId": 492, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 491}, {"answer": "Yeah, you have to -- I mean, it's business.", "docId": "120907pmt", "aSentId": 497, "question": "Take the cash when you can?", "qSentId": 496}, {"answer": "I'm very well.", "docId": "120907pmt", "aSentId": 526, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 525}, {"answer": "I'm disappointed actually because --", "docId": "120907pmt", "aSentId": 528, "question": "How are you doing?", "qSentId": 527}, {"answer": "I've just imagined I would meet the rebellious, explosive, spitfire, the angry young woman.", "docId": "120907pmt", "aSentId": 530, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 529}, {"answer": "Respectful.", "docId": "120907pmt", "aSentId": 543, "question": "You are, aren't you?", "qSentId": 542}, {"answer": "I can indeed.", "docId": "120907pmt", "aSentId": 551, "question": "You can vote in the American election?", "qSentId": 550}, {"answer": "I have voted long distance as I traveled.", "docId": "120907pmt", "aSentId": 553, "question": "Have you voted before?", "qSentId": 552}, {"answer": "My meaning is towards the spiritual activism, less the political one.", "docId": "120907pmt", "aSentId": 555, "question": "What is your leaning?", "qSentId": 554}, {"answer": "Well, I can share mine and then others.", "docId": "120907pmt", "aSentId": 571, "question": "When you travel around the world as you do, usually successfully, what impression do you get about America these days?", "qSentId": 570}, {"answer": "The Britain are the thoughtful, intellectual --", "docId": "120907pmt", "aSentId": 577, "question": "What is Britain?", "qSentId": 576}, {"answer": "I dare say.", "docId": "120907pmt", "aSentId": 581, "question": "Handsome?", "qSentId": 580}, {"answer": "I -- upon chatting with a lot of people around the planet, I think a lot of people are -- perceive America to be a little narcissistic and a little traumatized.", "docId": "120907pmt", "aSentId": 587, "question": "Have you detected it changing in the last few years?", "qSentId": 586}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "120907pmt", "aSentId": 591, "question": "You're into this attachment parenting, aren't you?", "qSentId": 590}, {"answer": "Almost.", "docId": "120907pmt", "aSentId": 604, "question": "Your son is two now, right?", "qSentId": 603}, {"answer": "Yeah, I do.", "docId": "120907pmt", "aSentId": 608, "question": "Do you mind me asking?", "qSentId": 607}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120907pmt", "aSentId": 610, "question": "Are you still breast feeding?", "qSentId": 609}, {"answer": "I live in the present moment.", "docId": "120907pmt", "aSentId": 612, "question": "Are you heading into the four or five-year-old breastfeeding possibility?", "qSentId": 611}, {"answer": "I would say I'm less reactive.", "docId": "120907pmt", "aSentId": 618, "question": "Now, how has marriage and parenting calmed you down?", "qSentId": 617}, {"answer": "I think anger can move worlds.", "docId": "120907pmt", "aSentId": 628, "question": "What's the most passionate when you've written a song ever?", "qSentId": 627}, {"answer": "Just this morning.", "docId": "120907pmt", "aSentId": 631, "question": "What was the song you wrote?", "qSentId": 630}, {"answer": "Yeah, reflecting on ex-boyfriends can bring that out in any woman I think, or any man, frankly.", "docId": "120907pmt", "aSentId": 634, "question": "When you look back, can you remember writing a big song that was just driven out sheer, blind fury?", "qSentId": 633}, {"answer": "We're also unfortunately have to get around to talking about music.", "docId": "120907pmt", "aSentId": 659, "question": "Who gets to say that?", "qSentId": 658}, {"answer": "It wasn't in real time, so it was super disconcerting.", "docId": "120907pmt", "aSentId": 666, "question": "What's that all about?", "qSentId": 665}, {"answer": "I would have said thank Christ; can I skip over all the hard part and wait for him.", "docId": "120907pmt", "aSentId": 682, "question": "If I said to you when you were a young Alanis in Canada, you're going to end up married to a rapper called Mario Soul Eye Treadway, and have a son called Ever, would you have believed me?", "qSentId": 681}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "120907pmt", "aSentId": 685, "question": "Is this true love for you?", "qSentId": 684}, {"answer": "Where your heart either aches or breaks.", "docId": "120907pmt", "aSentId": 698, "question": "So in love is a little bit of a tough term for me What does that even mean?", "qSentId": 697}, {"answer": "I was a love addict through and through.", "docId": "120907pmt", "aSentId": 701, "question": "So you're just a incurable romantic?", "qSentId": 700}, {"answer": "I was drawn to the back walking away, as the beautiful P.M. Melody (ph) would say in her book.", "docId": "120907pmt", "aSentId": 705, "question": "Were you drawn to constantly inappropriate men?", "qSentId": 704}, {"answer": "Values being the same.", "docId": "120907pmt", "aSentId": 720, "question": "How did you know this guy was for you?", "qSentId": 719}, {"answer": "I pray all the time.", "docId": "120907pmt", "aSentId": 736, "question": "Do you pray?", "qSentId": 735}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120907pmt", "aSentId": 741, "question": "The interview to end?", "qSentId": 740}, {"answer": "I don't know if compromise is actually the word.", "docId": "120907pmt", "aSentId": 753, "question": "Whereas the answer is probably compromise I would guess, right?", "qSentId": 752}, {"answer": "I love it.", "docId": "120907pmt", "aSentId": 760, "question": "Do you like being a celebrity?", "qSentId": 759}]